AdditionalNews ^{
    Regular0=Attention! Absolute Nothing happened on planet #pl1# today! We repeat - absolutely Nothing happened on planet #pl1#! Experts have already arrived at the location to assess and stabilize the situation. Do not panic under any circumstances, because panic is the most terrible enemy!
    Regular1=Due to the adoption on the planet #pl1# of very strict conservative laws prohibiting the sale, display and distribution of pornographic and erotic material, massive local spontaneous riots arose. All stores engaged in such activities urgently sell out their products, but demand does not decrease, and supply becomes more and more expensive!
    Regular10=Another strike of radical “greens” took place on planet #pl1#. The demonstrators demanded a reduction in the emission of chlorocarbons into the atmospheres of undeveloped planets and the abandonment of hyperjumps until a safe method of piercing space is invented. As before, after the participants drank cilantro juice, chaotic disturbances began. There are rumors in society around the world about an impending ban on such processions.
    Regular100=Furry terrorists: today residents of one of the regions of the planet #pl1# are faced with massive damage to infrastructure and fallen trees. The beaver invasion was to blame. Wet mammals, for some unknown reason, have filled the streets and attacked green areas. Zoologists have already begun to find out the reasons for this behavior.
    Regular101=Giveaway <clr>1.000.000.000<clrEnd> cr.! Only at GalaLoto - buy tickets and be guaranteed to win! The prize fund is more than 40 billion!<br>"GalaLoto" - they win against us!
    Regular102=“The Motherland is in danger!”<br>Today, Chairman of the Council of People's Commissars Aizif Zelazny, the leader of the socialist planet #pl1#, addressed the people with a fiery speech. Due to the increase in terrorist attacks and attempts to sabotage industrialization, the planet's government was forced to take action. Measures to suppress counter-revolutionary activities are being tightened and a curfew is being introduced. The security of security guards and other protected persons is being strengthened, street patrols by Red Army soldiers are being introduced, as well as the protection of infrastructure facilities by them.
    Regular103=“Do you want total anarchy?!”<br>Real mass psychosis is taking location on planet #pl1#. The propaganda campaign launched by local anarchists came to its logical conclusion - a proposal to the people to establish “total anarchy” on the planet. Economists of the Interstellar Economic Fund advise the rest of the planets in the sector to switch to importing the raw materials they need from other suppliers, because “total anarchy” will destroy both the planet’s economy and utopia itself, which will lead to total devastation and the impossibility of supplies.
    Regular104=Today the meteorite shower "Alseif-#count1#" passed through the upper layers of the planet's atmosphere #pl1#. Millions of residents were able to watch this spectacle, which will soon become part of local astronomical exhibitions and museums.
    Regular105=A quiet evening on planet #pl1# was literally torn apart by a guitar and a drum - the famous rock musician “Radio Operator” Tapchinsky came here with a new album. The audience greeted with an approving roar the songs “Tzufai”, “Operation Coalition Force”, “Song of the Radioactive Desert”, “Gralgar Troubles” and others, which have already become classics of rock music.
    Regular106=“Unheard-of parasitism and connivance”: this is how one of the officials of the planet #pl1# spoke about the state of the transport network in view of the publication of the results of the commission on the “Magnetoroad Workers Case”. The commission revealed almost complete non-compliance of vehicles and infrastructure with standards, complete non-compliance with schedules and other violations. The Minister of Transport has already been removed from his post, and the trial has begun.
    Regular107=A lonely officer of the Red-Crimson Army is looking for a fighting girlfriend. There are no preferences.
    Regular108=The People's Commissar for the National Economy of the Planet #pl1# reported to the Council of People's Commissars on the results of the Third Five-Year Plan. As part of the final stage of industrialization, a plan was also implemented to create a network of “small towns” that strengthened the infrastructure of rural areas. The chairman of the Council of People's Commissars praised the People's Commissariat, saying that such rapid pace of administrative and other types of work should set an example for other Commissariats.
    Regular109=Meeting in Davus: the economic forum of the Trade Alliance, an intersectoral economic association based on the structures of the Coalition, opened on planet #pl1#. At the forum, decisions will be discussed and made regarding the future policy of the Alliance, the acceptance and integration of new members. In addition, many small deals will be concluded during the forum, so all the nearby hotels are filled with representatives of the free planets of the Coalition.
    Regular11=The Galaxy Science Fiction Congress has opened on planet #pl1#. It was opened by honorary member of the Assembly of Fiction Stepan Karol with a speech about the “portable magic of books.” In total, at the start of the congress, more than twelve thousand participating writers were announced, because the congress is an excellent opportunity for young aspiring authors. As visitors say now, after just a few hours after the opening of the Congress, Arton Klisov’s book “Children of Eltan” became a real bolt from the blue, which, in the best traditions of Roger Zheleznyak’s school, tells the story in three space-time plot lines at once, with no intersections with each other having - a self-portrait line, the world line of the Eltan star shortly before the disaster and an alternative reality in which not only the Gaalians, but also the rest of the modern Coalition are evacuated from the Klissan threat from the neighboring sector. However, everyone here will find something to read!
    Regular110=Exhibition at #pl1#!<br>Today an exhibition of the latest achievements of the planets participating in the Coalition opened in one of the pavilions of #pl1#-Expo. Everything is presented here - ground weapons, starting from personal officer blasters to anti-aircraft armored trains with multiple launch rocket systems for space objects and portable shield generators - including for protecting the surrounding area from enemy attacks, space weapons - from auxiliary laser guns and cover fire batteries to powerful anti-material guns, and reconnaissance weapons - holoplanets with arsenals of various weapons and equipment, and much more. Also at the exhibition came designers who wanted to sell their patents at a higher price - or even get a job in an alien design bureau.
    Regular111=A unique event on planet #pl1# - a couple consisting of Field Marshal Bedilash, beloved by the Red Army Ramgatru, and Gaalian Moori Us held their wedding here.<br>The Field Marshal, always distinguished by eccentricity and originality in habits, behavior and decisions, surprised few people with such a choice of a life partner . Much more strange is the choice of the honorary representative of the diplomatic hull Duede and the famous Iike-baanist Moori.<br>For the festivities, the field marshal decided not to skimp and rented a whole palace, where he invited many guests of all races of the Coalition and threw a gigantic party. We wish the newlyweds happiness!
    Regular12=Recruitment is underway for flight training institutions. Payment for the course is made at the expense of the structures of the Coalition of Intelligent Races. For any questions, please contact the military registration office.
    Regular13=As a result of inspections by the Sanitary and Epidemiological Control, monstrous connivance against the rangers was revealed. The Galactic Council is forming a set of measures that should prevent this from happening in the future.
    Regular14=Today, a monument was unveiled on planet #pl1# dedicated to the daring raid of the recently deceased ranger Tarburym, as a result of which this system was liberated for the last time.
    Regular15=Today on planet #pl1# the closing ceremony of the Coalition Olympic Games took place. One of the members of the team of the winning planet in the medal standings, according to tradition, lit a torch from the Fire that had been burning throughout the Olympics, after which it went out - and will flare up on the next planet. 12 teams took part in these games - mostly from planets slightly affected by the war or occupied by the Dominators.
    Regular16=Police wave news! Thanks to the help of citizens on planet #pl1#, local law enforcement officers caught terrorists from the “Society of Witnesses of Dominators” sect. Those arrested stubbornly deny their involvement in the organization and their guilt in the terrorist attacks.
    Regular17=The believers of planet #pl1# are rejoicing - the famous medium Rabbi Vain visited their homeland. He took a short walk through some of the most famous religious sites on the planet, and gave a short speech about the need to abandon materialism and move towards humility and atonement.
    Regular18=Today on planet #pl1# at the Planetary Holographic Theater named after. Pirsov held a premiere - the very famous neoclassical symphony orchestra "Gideon" performed in front of the audience with new compositions - musical accompaniment to such giants of the old gaming industry as "Tears of Dali 10", "The Witcher 5", "Mystical Pagers 4", "Heroes of Sword and Shield 3", and many others. Critics have already skyrocketed the ratings.
    Regular19=Today on planet #pl1# the CCCLXXIV Congress of Communist Parties of the sector began. Those gathered discuss modern methods of struggle for workers' rights, as well as the results of the 20th Congress of the Communist Party of the Earth - as is known, the cradle of socialism.
    Regular2=Due to the explosive growth of the population on planet #pl1#, benefits and a series of concessions for large families have been cancelled. Pessimistic forecasts indicate the imminent need to introduce birth quotas.
    Regular20=Today a grandiose event has begun on planet #pl1# - the largest reconstruction festival in history has opened, in which for the first time medievalists and novumists, as well as “fantasyists,” as well as representatives from absolutely all races of the Coalition, will participate together. The festival will last just over a month and promises to be interesting - the organizers promise to reconstruct the battle of Kryas, Catalan Fields, Borodannye Fields, Plotava, Liptsek and many others. And most importantly, visitors will be treated to authentic cuisine from antiquity!
    Regular21=Today on planet #pl1# the championship for controlling modular robots has opened. The program features competition between participants for the title of best commander, fighting obviously extremely powerful opponents, completing special missions and much more!
    Regular22=The travel company "Blue Knash" offers tours at the lowest prices! From classic routes to extreme and completely new ones! If you have any questions, please contact the company's branch on the nearest planet of the Coalition.
    Regular23=“It is not by Alla’s will that cities fly with antigravity!” - said one of the radical religious leaders at the next meeting of the Al-Kokalla Coalition , banned on most of the planets. Law enforcement agencies of all free planets are on full alert to repel possible attacks by fanatics on anti-gravity generators.
    Regular24=The Galactic Council at an extraordinary meeting decided to expand the government appropriation program.
    Regular25=Today the Commission for the Suppression of Slavery issued its verdict against the Ro Berto Lley gang. The leader and his henchmen should be executed, and accomplices should receive from 15 to 50 years in labor camps. In view of the difficult situation in the judicial sphere of the Coalition activities, this verdict is very likely to become a death sentence. This incident will be further proof of the uncompromising nature of the Coalition fight against the remnants of slavery.
    Regular26=Today, representatives of planets #pl1#, #pl2# and #pl3# signed the Declaration “On Galactic Credit”, abolishing their own internal currency, the location of which will be taken by credit.
    Regular27=A parade in honor of the 825th anniversary of the end of the internecine war of local feudal lords has ended on planet #pl1#. This victory made it possible to unite the planet under a single command, which gave rise to the golden age of the colony.
    Regular28=The largest anti-war rally in the Galaxy is in full swing on planet #pl1#. Pacifists of all free planets demand that the Coalition sit down at the negotiating table with the Dominators. Despite opposition from the police, several clashes between protesters and militaristic spectators are known.
    Regular29=As a result of financial and administrative fraud, the Galactic Commonwealth Bank lost 245 million loans. The working version of the investigators is the use of inevitable “gaps” in the bank’s security systems and abuse of official powers by someone from the bank’s management.
    Regular3=Today on planet #pl1# the holo-award ceremony "Hoskar" took place. This time, the famous Dovvid Spireberk took away the golden statuette - it was awarded to the painting “Knash in the Fog”. Happy fans and compatriots are already waiting for the director on his home planet.
    Regular30=In the literal sense of this word, the struggle is flaring up around the Rodin nature reserve on the planet #pl1#. Soon after the colonization of this planet began, under pressure from the Galactic Council, almost its entire territory was recognized as a protected area. Naturally, this enormously reduced the area available for construction, and also put an end to mining. Local entrepreneurs were not satisfied with this, and they achieved the abolition of the reserve status of 280 square kilometers of the reserve in order to build a network of mines on this site. In response to this, the entire population of the planet took to the streets, blocking the path of the lumberjacks. As a sign of solidarity, environmental activists are arriving on the planet, which is why the government has canceled almost all interstellar flights. The Galactic Council has already stated that this topic will be raised at its next meeting. We will monitor developments.
    Regular31=Today, the Coalition of Intelligent Races suffered an incredible loss. The famous traveler and writer Fad Kon-Okh'khov died from the consequences of the Minimian fever. Fans of his work and achievements converge on his home on planet #pl1# to say goodbye to the famous personality. Three days of mourning have been declared on the planet, and all entertainment events have been cancelled.
    Regular32=Today, the Coalition of Intelligent Races suffered an incredible loss. The famous so-called “proletarian” writer and publicist Max Peshy died of a heart attack. Fans of his work converge on his home on planet #pl1# to say goodbye to the famous personality. Three days of mourning have been declared on the planet, and all entertainment events have been cancelled. Most socialist and communist organizations declared a week of “Memory of Max Pedestrian”.
    Regular33=A new speed record was set on the hyperspace path #star1#-#star2# - the stated distance was covered in a paltry 4 hours. The new record holder, Mahai Leminher, does not reveal the secret of such speed, but hints at the emergence of a new generation of Technology .
    Regular34=As part of the holography festival, the designers of Earth, #pl1# and #pl2# showed a new miracle of Technology: a giant (several cubic kilometers) holographic image that generates and shows realistic battles between the Coalition fleet and the Dominators.
    Regular35=An all-galactic sweets fair has opened on planet #pl1#. Confectioners and artisans from other branches of this food industry from all over the Galaxy share their experiences and recipes here. In the exotic section this time, representatives of all races of the Coalition, except for humans, are firmly observed.<br>Eat marshmallows,<br>Chew candy,<br>Eat and be happy,<br>Law-abiding citizen!
    Regular36=“Sentenced to 250 years in prison”: this was the verdict handed down by the planetary court of the planet #pl1# to the famous swindler Surey Mavaratti. His accomplice Lyakusha Shushkets also received 150 years of strict regime. Let us recall: Surey Mavaratti, as part of a criminal group, organized an “investment fund” that accepted citizens’ deposits at an incredible 1,500 percent or more per month. Despite the ancient history of this method, millions of citizens of the Coalition fell for this “bait”, and, according to unconfirmed information, even rangers! Come to your senses, Galaxy!
    Regular37=The Crump and Son corporation declared bankruptcy. Local managers will pay the local workers, and factory areas and equipment will be sealed before the auction begins. It is unknown how the disappearance of such a large metallurgical enterprise will affect it.
    Regular38=Planets #pl1#, #pl2# and #pl3# declared the creation of an All-System Socialist Commonwealth in the #star1# system. Representatives of the planets who signed the Commonwealth Treaty announced the beginning of a new era in the history of the system, opening up new horizons and enormous opportunities for integration and development.
    Regular39=The government of the planet #pl1# announced a boycott of trading with the planet #pl2# due to “xenophobic statements by the ruling circles of the planet.” Sanctions against planet #pl2# continue to multiply. How long will its economy last?
    Regular4=On planet #pl1#, strikes among logistics workers are raging. The proletarians are demanding an increase in hourly wages, which over the past few months have been reduced by the local monopolist Tyndex by 75 percent or more.
    Regular40=The Commission of Terraform Engineers announced the completion of the analysis of the situation on planet #pl1#. An extremely dry climate and newly discovered sources of toxic gases are seriously reducing the planet's habitability. To eliminate these problems, a weather station will be installed on the planet and a surface terraforming operation will be carried out, which will not require the resettlement of citizens.
    Regular41=An operation was carried out on planet #pl1# to arrest the so-called. "prophet" Mahammut. Having waited until the “pilgrim” was in the narrow alleys of the pre-occupied slums, law enforcement officers separated Mahamutt from the rest of the crowd, arrested him and, with the help of aircraft, transferred him to the upper levels of the capital complex. The “Saint” is charged with calls for the overthrow of the legitimate government on several planets, aggressive and xenophobic statements against other races of the Coalition, as well as statements about the need for the violent destruction of the institutions of the Coalition and its dissolution.
    Regular42=As a result of the coordinated work of Dzuhallaga, R7, the VRU (External Intelligence Directorate) and the NKGB (People's Committee for Galactic Security), the formation of the New Maloq-Peleng alliance was revealed and disrupted. Gaaldok, who had previously maintained neutrality in such matters, came under suspicion of supporting this initiative.
    Regular43=An extraordinary meeting of the Galactic Council took place today. There were many issues on the agenda, but a clear decision could only be made regarding one thing - a unanimously supported increase in funding for the MK Armed Forces.
    Regular44=The subspace channel "Mayak" announces its closure due to a drop in the number of listeners and the departure of most of the team. “We were glad to travel together at twenty-eight years,” the official representatives of the channel summed up their activities.
    Regular45=The Lubyanka Mirror partnership is recruiting specialists in the information technology field, graphic designers, quest, text and map makers, as well as arcade players. No work experience required. The Partnership also welcomes volunteers for product testing and public service and smaller analytical positions. For any questions, please contact the partnership office in Rostock, planet Earth.
    Regular46=Revolutions at the lowest prices - from two million credits! Colored, proletarian, nationalist, religious! Uprisings, riots and strikes of any duration! I will take on any situation, even the most stable one!
    Regular47=Tutor on Malestashinism. Inexpensive services for government members and other elites. For work in pre-revolutionary conditions, the cost of services triples.
    Regular48=On planet #pl1#, street battles between fascist-monarchist, anarchist-liberal blocs, etc. do not subside. "Left Front". The government, still beheaded, does nothing, and the population is in permanent fear of tomorrow.
    Regular49=Mining agency "Ostap" - we will get what, where and from anywhere, even from underground! Work with jammers of any complexity! The weight of the extracted object is limited to the carrying capacity of one healthy adult fish.
    Regular5=Several female white-haired Pallas cats, as well as two female karakumals, brought kittens to the cosmozoo of planet #pl1#. This is a joyful event for the employees, because these animals got into the cosmozoo just last year.
    Regular50=The Ministry of Defense of the planet #pl1# invites everyone to purchase the Kommersant-4 armored train. The train is equipped with several hundred guns with calibers ranging from 1250 to 40 mm, 25 standard Strizh PVRKO guns, as well as 4 Scimitar plasma orbital weapon . The train also contains a hangar with several ground-to-orbit fighter, bomber and attack squadrons, as well as location for six infantry divisions and two tank hull. For questions, please contact the planetary government hotline. The preliminary cost of the train is 45 million credits, negotiable.
    Regular51=The Kursecchatov research team has solemnly launched the first of ten reactors of the neutroantiquark power plant on planet #pl1#. According to calculations, the full launch of the structure will allow the planetary shield to be switched to a mode of complete protection against the introduction of objects from space, at the same time incinerating space debris.
    Regular52=Special offer! The Stereobifon company offers a comprehensive subscription to all existing media for only 3599 credits per month! From "Penchekryak around us" to "Quasi-quantum physics for the little ones!"! From "Ranger Truth" to "Dzuhallag Leaf"! Hurry up and subscribe!
    Regular53=The economic crisis on planet #pl1# has led to a colossal decline in population in just a few months, reports GIA Novosti. The government is making frantic attempts to stop the crisis, give people jobs and stabilize the situation with shortages of food and medicine through the rationing system, but the successes are hardly noticeable. Against the backdrop of these events, a sharp increase in the popularity of socialist and communist organizations is recorded.
    Regular54=At an extraordinary meeting, the Galactic Council condemned radical religious figures inciting the collapse of the Coalition as “an association of infidels denying the will of Alla.” This issue is now regulated by the Criminal Code of the Commonwealth of Intelligent Races and will be punishable by death.
    Regular55=The legendary all-galactic trivia game "What? Where? Why?" invites experts to participate in the qualifying round of the program. Participant reward - <clr>150<clrEnd> cr.! Hurry!
    Regular56=Tests of the so-called “smart” polymer have started on planet #pl1#. With its help, several space-to-space weapons were created. Next in line is the generation of hull. If this version of the polymer - Octoneir - passes the tests, then the Armed Forces of our Coalition will be equipped much better!
    Regular57=By decision of the Galactic Council, the 63rd commission will meet on planet #pl1# in the case of the execution of the Emperor of the Khoot sector. This issue has not been resolved for more than three hundred years, and now the attacks of neo-imperialists have been mixed in with historical and political issues. Let us hope that this commission will finally end this protracted series of meetings.
    Regular58=Based on the results of the draw, planet #pl1# will become the new location for the Akkar-1 race. The government of the planet has already announced the start of preparations for hosting the galactically famous competition.
    Regular59=Reshuffles in the Galactic Council! The Earth Envoy has been recalled and a replacement has not yet been appointed. The reason for the recall of the patriot and master negotiator #Molotov# is still unknown.
    Regular6=As a result of the coordinated actions of Galapol employees and local services, an entire network of drug dealers was busted on planet #pl1#. According to local authorities, this operation also revealed a whole “bouquet” of corruption mechanisms. New, extremely severe measures of struggle should discourage at least the desire to associate with criminals and thus glorify the planet.
    Regular60=The causeless glaciation of the planet #pl1# continues! So long some scientists are looking for the cause of the cataclysm, others are trying hard to stop it with the help of greenhouse and heat shields, as well as weather stations. Nevertheless, the population flees to the equator, and from there, those who are richer and more connected, to other planets. Due to massive private and government evacuations, the cost of tickets from the planet and the occupancy of transport have increased beyond belief.
    Regular61=Attention! Today, without a declaration of war, the landing forces of the planet's Armed Forces #pl1# landed on the surface of #pl2# and entered into battle with the local territorial defense. Local authorities urgently convened a militia, which entered the battle together with the numerically outnumbered terrorist defense forces. Meanwhile, the #pl1# fleet shelled the capital, and flights of bombers dropped charges on major cities of the planet. The victims of these attacks already number in the tens of thousands. The government of the planet #pl1# announced that this was a special anti-terrorist operation, but this argument is unlikely to convince the Galactic Council, which has just gathered for an emergency meeting.
    Regular62=A wave of rallies against leading meteorologists swept across the planet #pl1#. Participants blame them for reducing sunshine by an average of 20-40%, which has sharply increased the outflow of tourists. The technicians blame everything on the purchased Peleng parts instead of the production of the human-Faeyan concern Blau Front. How this will end is unknown, but we must find a “scapegoat” for the crowd!
    Regular63=Sizzling heat, hail and more than 300 mm of precipitation in the form of snow in one night - this is the price of a corporate party for homeless meteorologists at the Central weather point of the planet #pl1#. The proletarians who celebrated the birthday of three employees at once consumed an excessive amount of strong drinks, after which they caused significant mischief in the Sphere of Management. The emergency services showed the maximum level of preparation and coordination and did not allow civilian casualties.
    Regular64=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-Grad: +13.. +16, partly cloudy. Atm. pressure: 758 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 57%.
    Regular65=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-Grad: +21.. +25, clear. Atm. pressure: 767 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 32%.
    Regular66=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-Grad: +5.. +9, rain is expected in places, wind - 5-7 m/s. Atm. pressure: 749 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 82%.
    Regular67=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-City: -2.. +3, hail is expected in places, wind - 2-4 m/s. Atm. pressure: 744 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 79%.
    Regular68=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-Grad: -12.. -9, cloudy, snow expected. Atm. pressure: 751 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 57%.
    Regular69=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-Grad: -15.. -7, snow is expected, wind - 7-9 m/s. Atm. pressure: 739 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 98%.
    Regular7=On planet #pl1# the summit of planets participating in the Third Defense Sector ended. Representatives of the planets signed a series of agreements that should improve the relationship between the armed forces of the sectors.
    Regular70=Weather in the capital complex #pl1#-Grad: +14.. +17, heavy rain is expected, wind - 1-3 m/s, gusts up to 11 m/s. Atm. pressure: 740 mm Hg. Art. Relative humidity: 100%.
    Regular71=As a result of the so-called “counter-terrorist” operation, the authorities of the planet #pl1# failed to catch the famous revolutionary <clr>Chen Gekarra<clrEnd>. Despite the fact that Chen was several times almost under the noses of the operatives, puffing on the eternal cigar, the military still missed him. The rebels all over the planet rejoice and begin a new series of attacks - so, under the pressure of the proletariat, the Livre fortifications finally fell. We continue to monitor the incredibly tense situation on this planet.
    Regular72=Attention to all posts and concerned citizens of the Coalition! One of the Faeyan transport ships leaving the #star1# system is carrying on board a dangerous criminal - Ern Teludnov, who “distinguished himself” in setting fire to the parliament building on one of the planets and calling for the overthrow of the legally elected government on the planets of the local systemic community. Those who handed over the scoundrel to the authorities of any of the planets of the system will receive <clr>35,000<clrEnd> cr., those who destroyed - <clr>20,000<clrEnd>!
    Regular73=18.VI.3367 in the exhibition hall #pl1# an award ceremony will be held on the occasion of the anniversary of the victory in the war with the Klissans. All rangers - arrive in full dress uniform!<br>B.A. Bavangaev
    Regular74=The energy crisis on planet #pl1# is flaring up with renewed vigor!<br>After terrorists blew up several of the most important energy and logistics hubs, the planet's leadership was forced to shut down a significant part of the power plants, reducing the level of energy production to a minimum. Now terrorists are sabotaging the restoration of energy supply networks. The level of dissatisfaction among the population, which has been without electricity for more than two weeks, is colossal.
    Regular75=Today, during a meeting of the lower house of the Parliament of the planet #pl1#, armed people with red armbands burst into the hall and declared the illegitimacy of the government and its arrest. In a short time, unknown persons “arrested” the entire planetary control apparatus. No more information was received from the planet.
    Regular76=This morning, the president of the planet #pl1# Nerensky was killed by a shot from a hand-held plasma gun. The already economically and politically unstable situation on the planet has once again shaken. Many settlements are already occupied by strengthened radicals.
    Regular77=The next government-ethnic crisis on planet #pl1# led to the collapse of the planetary formation into small, agonizing regional associations. The ongoing bombing of the planet as part of Operation Alliance Power is causing increasing indignation among the galactic community. Volunteer fighter regiments are increasingly resisting the bomber fleet - but will the government decide to withdraw troops?
    Regular78=The planned reduction of wages in several sectors of the planet's economy #pl1# led to a wave of indignation among workers.<br>The government claims that such measures should prevent further progression of inflation and the emergence of a crisis.
    Regular79=Inflation on planet #pl1# has reached a record 10^35%!<br> So long economists blame the sluggish government for the troubles, the population is essentially left without wages and means of subsistence. Cases of spontaneous organization with the aim of evenly distributing essential products among locals are becoming more frequent. The Galactic Economic Fund is expected to intervene in the situation.
    Regular8=At the celebration of the 117th anniversary of the socialist revolution, the representative of the Earth, Volodya Lenivin, made a colossal criticism of the current situation in the Galaxy. Drawing an analogy with a number of states of the past, he stated the need to establish a regime of total mobilization and planned interaction with enterprises for a speedy victory over the dominators.
    Regular80=Today the joint exercises of the fleets of the planets #pl1# and #pl2# within the framework of the Corvus-14 agreement ended. Representatives of the planets say that, despite some ideological differences, the friendship of peoples is insurmountable and will only grow stronger.
    Regular81=Accusations of sabotage, counter-revolutionary activities and treason are the three main articles of the fourth Sal trial, taking place on planet #pl1#.<br>A series of large-scale trials has a very specific reason behind it - the recently ended civil war and the beginning of the REP - Restorative Economic Policy. To eliminate cases of abuse of power, representatives of the Coalition, vested with a wide range of powers, are present at all processes.
    Regular82=Opening of a new branch of Chesnoil - now we are on planet #pl1#! The best fuel in the Galaxy conquers new heights!<br><br>Chesoil - quality since 2997!
    Regular83=And on planet #pl1# clashes between “blue” and “black” do not stop!<br>Despite half a century and three changes of power/course, civil war continues to torment the planet’s population, splitting it into many small and large groups, the main group of which called the "Cursed Rainbow" - "red", "blue", "green", "black", "brown", "white" and "yellow". And what are the fanatics of the Order of the Hospitaller worth, albeit small in number, but equal in deed to any of the “flowers”? However, one thing is clear - the political situation on the planet is unstable, and perhaps only the deployment of coalition troops can correct this.
    Regular84=Frightening news: the ex-Prime Minister of the planet #pl1# Annek Malloni was kidnapped from her own home in the suburbs of Turpol.<br>The investigation has so far refused to comment, but, most likely, the “Red Stripes” are to blame for this, thus avenging the arrests many leftist nationalist Mallonee
    Regular85=The urban areas of the planet #pl1# are in chaos!<br>Crowds of gangsters exchanging fire that appeared as if out of nowhere turned out to be an impossible task for the security forces. Despite the colossal losses and the deployment of the army, there are still too many criminals!
    Regular86=In conditions of total suppression of any manifestation of dissent by the regime of planet #pl1#, an underground coalition of socialists, democrats and radical liberal pacifists was formed. Clashes between security forces and party members are occurring more and more often. The situation on the planet is tense to the limit and threatens an imminent “explosion”.
    Regular87=The planetary founding celebration is taking place today on planet #pl1#. On this day six centuries ago, the first colonists first set foot on earth, building the first planetary administration on this site.
    Regular88=The People's Commissariat of Agriculture of the Planet #pl1# reported on the results of the implementation of its part of the IV Five-Year Plan. As a result, breakthrough farming methods were introduced, developed jointly by the 7th Interstellar, which made it possible to free up more than a thousand square kilometers of ineffective arable zones for nature reserves.
    Regular89=Fire in the business center "#center#" on planet #pl1#! At the moment, #count1# of deaths are known. The Amount of victims is unknown; the numbers mentioned by eyewitnesses vary greatly. The preliminary cause of the incident is non-compliance with fire safety standards. Of particular concern is the building's roof material, which releases toxic compounds when burned in conditions of excess carbon dioxide.
    Regular9=The planetary court of planet #pl1# opened a case in connection with an administrative violation of the alien citizen Li Xi Qin. This subject entered a secure facility and destroyed the entire cargo of the super-exotic Chuke-Puksa, declaring that the insult to the Great Hunter was a sign of the eternal enmity of the Puzilanders with the cowardly people of the planet. Therefore, a strategically important fruit must be immediately destroyed - that is, eaten.
    Regular90=Uncontrolled elements!<br>Fire planets #pl1# are fighting with all their might against the all-consuming flames that are destroying the Verkhnelinsky forest area. The most likely cause of the incident is the ignition of dry vegetation from artificial fire sources.
    Regular91=Today on planet #pl1# members of the so-called Galactic Left Front carried out a raid and a series of massacres of members of the "Union in Faith" and the "Human Imperial Party" - two extreme right-wing organizations. Those who committed lynching have been put on the wanted list, but the fact remains that the political situation on the planet is tense to the limit.
    Regular92=A robbery of unprecedented impudence!<br>Today on planet #pl1# there was a raid on a branch of the Coalition Intergalactic bank. The attackers killed the guards and broke into the bank building. Taking advantage of the confusion, they broke into the bank vault, forced one of the employees to open it, and before the police arrived, they took out jewelry and money worth more than <clr>#count1#.000.000<clrEnd> cr.!
    Regular93=The study of the remains of a depleted star continues to fuel debate among scientists. The ultra-dense crystalline structure of the supposed “core” of the star, traces of radioactive metals that are unstable under normal conditions, and much more attract specialists from the entire Arm to planet #pl1#, where, in fact, laboratories for studying the dead star are organized.
    Regular94=VKS Day is celebrated today on planet #pl1#. The leader of the planet has already made a solemn speech to citizens and military personnel, and right now the VKS parade begins, which can be viewed on all official platforms anywhere in the Galaxy!
    Regular95=Today the construction of the Azirium complex on planet #pl1# was completed. This complex includes a huge spaceport of intersectoral importance, several cargo terminals, repair berths and even construction docks, as well as colossal warehouses. This complex will significantly improve connectivity in the region.
    Regular96=The local economic crisis on planet #pl1# threatens to develop into a sectoral catastrophe!<br>The collapse of the local quasi-currency market two weeks ago was greeted with a grin, but when large banks began to declare bankruptcy, deciding to “hit the jackpot” on investments in this area, it became no time for jokes. Due to the specific lending system, most enterprises and banks are mutually loaned, and payments are made gradually. The lack of payments has brought the entire economy of the planet, the financial center of the sector, to the brink of collapse.
    Regular97="The mystery of the Erashi language has been solved!" - this statement was made today by the famous linguist and amateur archaeologist Anetsy Serditov. According to his theory, the Erashi language should be viewed through the prism of Kichinay, which had a strong influence on Erashi before being pushed into history, if it was not even one of its progenitors.<br>Veneritized Erashistologists reacted to Serditov’s statements with great skepticism - firstly , all examples of “translations” are far-fetched, since in different cases the translations of the same word vary greatly, and the number of synonyms is incredibly vast. Secondly, this method has a long history of use, including in attempts to unravel Erashian, and has not been successful. Thirdly, If the people of Erashia belong to the Yauropean civilization, then the Kichinay people belong to the Andochina civilization, that is, they could not be the ancestors of the Erashians. However, this will not hinder Serditov’s fans and conspiracy theorists in their new “research.”
    Regular98=The Ministry of Agriculture of the planet #pl1# reported today on the harvest of a record grain harvest. Thanks to excellent conditions, new technologies and hard work, it was possible to harvest #count1# trillion tons of grain. The excess will go to foreign markets, thus replenishing the planet's budget.
    Regular99=Schools, universities, a research institute and much more - today the so-called “scientific district” was inaugurated on planet #pl1#. According to the project, it will provide neighboring microdistricts with the missing educational places and improve the scientific situation of the planet.
    RegularNewsCount=111
}
NotMagazineYearNews ^{
    News1=According to the Galactic Emergency Department, monthly inflation has now been reduced to just 0.#countYearly#% thanks to the Council's successful actions! It’s good to see positive dynamics at least in the economy.
    News2=According to the Galactic Emergency Department, monthly inflation currently stands at 2.#countYearly#%. Unfortunately, the Council failed to sufficiently stabilize the economy...
    News3=According to the Galactic Emergency Department, monthly inflation has now reached as much as 6.#countYearly#% due to the failure of the Council's actions! So long our enemies are attacking us, on the other side illiterate economists are attacking us.
}
WarNews ^{
    NewsAttack1=New messages are coming to us from planet #pl1#!<br>During a joint attack by the Navy, Aerospace Forces and amphibious forces, Feian fighters managed to regain control over cities in the surface waters!
    NewsAttack2=Another breakthrough!<br>The Faeyan government of planet #pl1# reports that as a result of the action of amphibious forces, deep fortifications and other military structures of the separatists were captured. The army continues to clear bunkers, and soldiers are preparing for new breakthroughs.
    NewsAttack3=Important messages from planet #pl1#!<br>During the ongoing battles, the Feian landing force managed to seize the passage to the ultra-deep Peleng shelters. So long the fighters are methodically clearing the territory, one thing is clear - the Peleng government has fled the planet, because the resistance offered to the Feian fighters is extremely chaotic.
    NewsBomb=Against the backdrop of the outbreak of war on planet #pl1#, an extraordinary meeting of the Galactic Council began. He will have to make a decision regarding this conflict and draw up a set of measures that will bring the end of the clashes closer.<br>Meanwhile, the Faeyan Aerospace Forces began deep bombing of the Peleng cities. The separatist government, convened by the Pelengs immediately after the declaration of war on the Faeyans, does not report casualties among the civilian population.
    NewsCounter1=We continue to inform about what is happening on the planet #pl1#!<br>As a result of successful reconnaissance and paratrooper actions during heavy battles, the separatists managed to knock out government troops from the territory of near-surface cities.
    NewsCounter2=Breaking news from planet #pl1#!<br>The coordinated actions of the partisans and the separatist army led to the loss of a bridgehead by government troops in deep fortifications. The Faeyan were forced to retreat to surface waters. Now the separatists are clearing out the last pockets of resistance, but we can already say for sure that the Faeyans were defeated.
    NewsEndDiplomacy=Attention!<br>Today, without waiting for the Faeyan invasion, the separatist government of planet #pl1# decided to surrender. The Galactic Council strongly approves of the actions of the separatists and has already allocated part of the funds to the Feian government for the restoration of the planet.
    NewsEndOnWayToVictory=As a result of a series of negotiations, due to the ongoing conflict on planet #pl1#, peace was signed!<br>Despite concessions from the separatists, the Faeyans perceive this peace not just as a Pyrrhic victory, but as pure humiliation. Confidence in the government was greatly undermined.
    NewsEndRevolution=Reports from the planet #pl1# - due to the dissatisfaction of the masses with the current policies of the planet's government, as well as failures in the war with the Peleng government, power was seized by the people's nominees. The revolutionary government first issued decrees on Earth and Peace; the latter ends the war going on on the planet according to the principle of “without indemnities and reparations.” The galactic public is somewhat shocked by this outcome of events.
    NewsEndViaWar=During the military actions of the Faeyan government of planet #pl1#, the separatist Peleng government was forced to flee the planet. Despite loud statements that, supposedly, “they will return!”, there are no prospects for victory over the Feian armed forces. The Faeyan leadership, with the support of the Galactic Council, began a series of tribunals over the Peleng commanders.
    NewsFisrtAttack=Breaking news from planet #pl1#!<br>Due to the refusal of the separatist government to admit defeat and cease resistance, the Headquarters of the Supreme High Command decided to begin landing in near-surface cities. The Peleng forces - as expected - did not put up strong resistance in the fight for these settlements. Apparently, most of the residents were evacuated in advance, so now these cities are deserted and bombed.
    NewsInterventionStarts=Important news from the Galactic Council: in view of the ongoing conflict on planet #pl1#, a decision was made to send in allied troops on the side of the Feian government. The contingent's arrival is expected within a couple of weeks.
    NewsMoreBombs=During the operation carried out on planet #pl1#, the Feian Aerospace Forces used super-depth charges for the first time. The target was the Peleng submarines. The task was completed successfully.
    NewsStart=Today has come the end of the deterioration of relations between the Faeyan citizens inhabiting the surface of the planet #pl1# and the depths of the planet Peleng citizens. Peleng forces bombarded all Faeyan ports and attacked their navy. A significant portion of the ships were damaged or sunk. The official leadership of the planet - the Faeyans - declared the impossibility of condoning such aggression. Some of the planets of the Coalition have already begun to express solidarity with one side or another. The Faeyan government declared martial law.
    NewsTerract=On planet #pl1#, counterintelligence prevented a terrorist attack in the planetary holotheater "Rodina". The Peleng terrorist is most likely an envoy of the separatists. His connection with the enemies of the official government is being established, but the public is already outraged - after all, they are sure that these Pelengs have once again shown what they are ready for for their goals.
    NewsTryToAttack=Condemnation of the separatists and the governments supporting them - this decision was made by the Galactic Council following its meeting regarding what was happening on planet #pl1#.<br>The separatists themselves attempted to land in one of the most damaged Faeyan ports. Alas, the Faeyan fleet has now been almost completely repaired, even the sunken ships, and the landing force was destroyed on the way. The Faeyan Headquarters announces the possibility of launching an operation to seize the Peleng territory.
}
FinancicalNews ^{
    NewsCredits1=A large number of loan users stabilized the loan rate. Trade has picked up noticeably.
    NewsCredits2=The Clan's constant victories led to the loss of many financial centers of the Coalition, which seriously destabilized credit.
    NewsCredits3=Alas, the Coalition locked-in position is not at all conducive to the development of credit, which is slowly withering away without trade flows.
    NewsMagazine=The annual "Financial Sheet" - for readers throughout the Galaxy - since 3011!<br><clr><clrEnd><br>#VPK#<br><clr><clrEnd><br>#Credit#<br><clr><clrEnd><br>#Minfin#
    NewsMinFin1=To increase the efficiency of financial work, the financial support department of the Interstellar Coalition carried out a reform of membership fees.
    NewsMinFin2=There is still no change on the Coalition financial front.
    NewsMinFin3=Due to a lack of funds, the Galactic Council curtailed some initiatives. The released funds will be used to build new ships.
    NewsMinFin4=Due to a lack of funds, the Galactic Council increased membership dues. The agricultural planets and their governments found themselves in an extremely difficult situation.
    NewsMinFin5=The improved situation at the front led to the release of significant funds by the Galactic Council. Membership fees were reduced, and the remaining funds were spent on creating a fleet in the liberated systems.
    NewsVPK1=A series of Coalition victories has led to higher prices for defense industry shares. Great time to sell shares!
    NewsVPK2=The unchanged front led to an audit of CAFIC expenses. A series of corruption schemes were exposed, and funds were freed up by stopping financing of low- or ineffective projects. Funds were invested in more promising areas, which increased the value of shares of military enterprises.
    NewsVPK3=The Coalition constant defeats led to an overstrain of its military-industrial complex, the loss or closure of some enterprises, which is why the price of shares of defense enterprises fell sharply - almost collapsed.
}
SmugglerNews ^{
}
ScienceNews ^{
    NewsBreak=Unfortunately, due to the military clashes that began in the #star1# system, the consultation of engineers and physicists on planet #pl1# was completed ahead of schedule.
    NewsEnd=Today the consultation of engineers and physicists on planet #pl1# ended. The result of their activities was the decision to focus on the development of plasma weapons and fraud with antimatter. Physicists also shared some advanced technologies with local specialists, which will undoubtedly help local science.
    NewsStart=Great news from planet #pl1#! Despite the current military situation, scientists from different planets of the Coalition continue their meetings! Representatives of #count1# free Sleeve star systems came together to hold a consultation on the further development of military engineering and related fields in the light of the latest achievements in the field of physics. Let's wish them good luck!
}
ColdWarNews ^{
    ColdWarAmericanArmy=.
    ColdWarAmericanRefugee=.
    ColdWarArms1=.
    ColdWarArms2=.
    ColdWarArms3=.
    ColdWarArmsRace=.
    ColdWarPanamianCrysis=.
    ColdWarSatteliteAttack=.
    ColdWarSovietArmy=.
    ColdWarSovietRefugee=.
    ColdWarSpiesCought=.
    ColdWarStart=Work in process. Wait for 1.5.0 "Die Festigung"
    ColdWarTerract=.
    ColdWarUSAMcCarthyism=.
    ColdWarUSAMobilization=.
    ColdWarUSAStopDiplo=.
    ColdWarUSAWin1=.
    ColdWarUSAWin2=.
    ColdWarUSAWin3=.
    ColdWarUSSRArrestDiplo=.
    ColdWarUSSRDissidents=.
    ColdWarUSSRMobilization=.
    ColdWarUSSRWin1=.
    ColdWarUSSRWin2=.
}
ImprovedRevoltNews ^{
    BadReforms=The measures taken by the government of planet #pl1# to stabilize the economy have failed. The passivity of the government leads to anger among the people and an increase in anti-government sentiment.
    CoalitionOfSocDemRevolt=The unstable situation on planet #pl1# became even more unstable - the Provisional Government was overthrown by the united forces of democrats, socialists and moderate anarchists. What will happen next is anyone's guess.
    CoolReforms=The government of planet #pl1# finally managed to stabilize the economic situation. The peak of the crisis has been passed. The number of unemployed is gradually decreasing, the work of public services is being restored, and the supply of enterprises is being improved.
    FirstRevolt=Attention! Today on planet #pl1#, as a result of an armed uprising, the government resigned. Now the future fate of the planet will be decided by the Provisional Government.
    FixingSituationDem=Moderate reforms and the transition of most of the opposition to the ranks of governments of the planet #pl1# bore fruit - gradually the economic situation on the planet leveled out, and unemployment began to decline.
    FixingSituationDic=The semi-dictatorial administration of the Provisional Government bore fruit. Gradually, nationalized enterprises launched other production facilities, which gave impetus to the economy. The situation on planet #pl1# has become calm again.
    FixingSituationSoc=The hard hand of the party and state security services eliminated the troublemakers and shifted the planet's production to the tracks it needed. In the shortest possible time, the new government restored old production facilities and almost forcibly launched the economy. This made it possible to stop the fall into the abyss and restore the provision of the population with everything necessary.
    Hunger=Attention! On planet #pl1#, due to the wrong actions of the government, real famine has begun! Food imports do not cover expenses; insignificant food reserves in spare warehouses are sold for pennies.
    OctoberRevolt=The unstable situation on planet #pl1# became even more unstable - the Provisional Government was dispersed by the Red Turbans assault force. Other administrative offices were also stormed and occupied by the local union of leftist forces.
    TryToReform=Today the government of the planet #pl1# announced the beginning of reforms due to the total economic recession and political stagnation. A number of measures are aimed at organizing public works and nationalizing some enterprises in order to revive the economy.
}
RangerDeathNews ^{
    Death1=Today we received news of a terrible event. Ranger #Ranger#, one of the best rangers in the Hulls, was killed today. CAFIC has already announced a reward for the killer's head.
    Death2=Attention! One of the best rangers of the #Ranger# Hulls fell victim to his enemies today. It is a pity that in such difficult days for the Coalition such fighters are lost.
    Death3=Defenders of the Coalition! Today is not the time to tremble before the enemy! One of the most desperate and brave fighters for the freedom of the inhabitants of the Inhabited Arm, #Ranger#, fell in battle today. Mourning has been declared throughout the territory controlled by the Council
}
CelebrationEvents ^{
    CelebrateCoalitionDeath=Residents of the Galaxy!<br>The Supreme Baron congratulates you on the #count# anniversary of the victory over the Dominators!<br>End of communication
    CelebrateDomiksClan=Residents of the Galaxy!<br>The Supreme Baron congratulates you on the #count# anniversary of the victory over the Dominators!<br>End of communication
    CelebrateDomiksCoal=Residents of the Galaxy!<br>We are glad to congratulate you on the #count# anniversary of the victory over the Dominators!<br><br>The war became a difficult test for the Coalition, but by uniting, we were able to overcome our enemies and become even stronger. Happy holiday!
    CelebratePiratesDeath=Residents of the Galaxy!<br>We are glad to congratulate you on the #count# anniversary of the victory over the pirate Clan!<br><br>The civil war and the split in society became a difficult test against the backdrop of the fight against the Dominators
    DomiksDefeated=Residents of the Coalition!<br>Today, #date#, we are pleased to announce that the efforts of the Armed Forces and the Ranger Hulls have put an end to the Dominator threat! The remnants of the enemy fleet no longer pose a serious threat to the Coalition and are gradually being destroyed by patrols.<br>From this day on, the Galactic Council stops the emergency measures aimed at countering the Dominators and begins discussing a set of measures to restore the Coalition territories from the Dominator occupation. The war with the Dominators is over!<br><br>Eternal glory to the soldiers who fell in battle with the invaders, and to those who are protecting our peace right now!
    GalaxyCleanedFromDomiks=Residents of the Inhabited Arm!<br>Today, #date#, we are pleased to announce that on the territory of the Arm there are no longer systems occupied by dominator invaders!<br><br>Glory to the soldiers who fell in the fight for the liberation of the planets of the Coalition!
    GalaxyCleanedFromPirates=Residents of the Inhabited Sleeve!<br>Today, #date#, we are pleased to announce that the threat from the pirate Clan has been completely eliminated!<br>There is no longer a single system left under the control of the pirates, and the remnants of the pirate groups are being destroyed by soldiers of the CAFIC special forces. <br><br>Glory to the soldiers who fell in the fight for the liberation of the planets of the Coalition!
}
MobilizationEvents ^{
    En_garde1=Attention!<br><br>Due to the worsening situation on the fronts, the Galactic Council has announced another wave of mobilization. All citizens with a pilot's license must report to the assembly point.
}
GalaxyNews ^{
    MaxCntPlanetNews=180
}
InprisonmentNews ^{
    Ranger=Today on planet Planet, FullName was convicted. He appeared in court on a range of charges. The court decided to teach the scoundrel a lesson and assigned him Month months arrest without confiscation of property.
    Ranger1=For the whole Month months strict prison regime thundered FullName. The authorities of the Star system had been looking for him for a long time, and he finally surrendered on the planet Planet.
    Ranger2=Today on the planet Planet the court hearing in the case of the ranger FullName ended. The planet's authorities confronted him with many atrocities, and it was decided to assign him Month months imprisonment.
}
MedalNews ^{
    Ceremony1=Today, the Galactic Council considered the applications of the CAFIC to reward the best rangers of the Hulls. This time the jury was extremely impressed by the achievements of ranger #name#. A brave fighter against the enemies of the Coalition will be awarded a #medal# on the nearest planet under the control of the CRR.
    Ceremony2=The time has come to reward the best representatives of the Hulls - this is what Ranger #name# has become, according to the Galactic Council. A well-deserved reward awaits him on the nearest inhabited planet - #medal#!
    Ceremony3=The worthy must always be rewarded - and Ranger #name# is awarded the badge of honor - #medal# according to the decision of the Galactic Council. Hooray!
}
ShipInfo ^{
    AddInfo ^{
        CustomInfos ^{
            CatchingDeath ^{
                Description=Information for death detection of the best rangers
                Icon=0
                Name=
                OnActCode ^{
                    01=int rnd = Rnd(1,3);
                    02=if(rnd == 1) AddPlanetNews(Format(CT('RangerDeathNews.Death1'),'#Ranger#',ShipName(ScriptItemActShip())));
                    03=if(rnd == 2) AddPlanetNews(Format(CT('RangerDeathNews.Death2'),'#Ranger#',ShipName(ScriptItemActShip())));
                    04=if(rnd == 3) AddPlanetNews(Format(CT('RangerDeathNews.Death3'),'#Ranger#',ShipName(ScriptItemActShip())));
                }
                OnActCodeTypes=t_OnDeath
            }
        }
    }
}
Script ^{
    Mod_RefNews ^{
        0= The Bertor Assassin
        1=The achievements of ranger name in the fight against the extremely dangerous strategic ships of the Dominators - Bertors - did not remain unnoticed by the Galactic Council. For his valor, the ranger was assigned a new award, and among his colleagues he is already called the Killer of Bertors!
    }
}
BertorThanks ~{
    1=The achievements of ranger name in the fight against the extremely dangerous strategic ships of the Dominators - Bertors - did not remain unnoticed by the Galactic Council. For his valor, the ranger was nominated for a new award, and among his colleagues he is already called "Bertor Killer"!
    Rank=The Bertor Assassin
}
